JACK CEBALLOS

Miami, FL 33176

Phone: (305) 772 -1065 | Email: jackrceballos@gmail.com

LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/JackCeballosMIA | GitHub: https://github.com/jceb30198

Portfolio: https://jceb30198.github.io/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a bachelors in International Business Administration seeking to learn more about the programming world. A month before graduating from Florida International University, the pandemic hit and an opportunity to take on a new challenge arose with the University of Miami Full-Stack Development Bootcamp. With a past of building computers for family members, the next step was to explore the world of website development. After working in the hospitality and production industry for the past 6 years there are skills that are transferable into the tech industry such as: listening to those that are more knowledgeable in order to learn new skills at a faster pace, communicating with a team to achieve a mutual goal, and adapting to new environments along with any problems that may have been unfamiliar in the past.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, NoSQL **Applications:** MySQL, MongoDB, GitHub, Heroku

Tools: Bootstrap, Google Fonts - Icons, Font Awesome, Materialize, Node.js, Express,

Handlebars, React

PROJECTS

Note Taker | RepositoryLink: https://github.com/jceb30198/Note_Taker | Deployed Link: https://ancient-island-96365.herokuapp.com/

- An application that allows the user to write down notes, save them to view later, and once the notes are done being used they can be deleted
- Tools/Languages: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Font Awesome, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Express.js

Mood Queue | https://github.com/jceb30198/Mood_Queue | https://jceb30198.github.io/Mood Queue/

- Tools/Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Materialize, Deezer API
- Authors: Jack Ceballos, Tomas Utreras, Nicholas Monplaisir
- An application where the user is able to click on a mood and find music to satisfy how
 they are feeling at the moment, the user is also able to search for any artist they prefer
 and listen to a sample of their song

Handlebars Burger | RepositoryLink: https://github.com/jceb30198/Handlebars_Burger | Deployed Link:https://limitless-forest-28943.herokuapp.com/

- An application that allows the user to add burgers to a "to eat" list and once the eat button is clicked the burger will go into the "devoured" list
- Tools/Languages: HTML, CSS, Materialize, Google Fonts, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Express.js, Express-Handlebars

Employee Manager | https://github.com/jceb30198/Management System

Tools/Languages: JavaScript, Node.is, Inquirer, MySQL, SQL, Console.Table

• A command line application that helps the user manage their employees along with the roles and departments that might be involved in the user's company

Weather Dashboard | Repository Link: https://github.com/jceb30198/Weather_Dashboard | Deployed Link: https://jceb30198.github.io/Weather_Dashboard/

- A web application that allows users to search the weather for their city of choice
- Tools/Languages: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Font Awesome, JavaScript, jQuery

EXPERIENCE

Lead Cellar-Man Unbranded Brewing Company

2020 - Present

Hialeah, FL

- Reduced product loss in order to optimize production output to 150-200 BBLs per month
- Communicated with the brewing team to plan production days and ran key metrics related to final product volume
- Organized the packaged product in the walk-in refrigerator while preparing and sending orders for distribution
- Monitored all products inside fermentation vessels and brite tanks until they were ready for packaging
- Maintained production responsibilities alongside the head brewer in order to meet the product yield goal

Cellar-Man MIA Beer Company 2019 – 2020

- Beer Company Miami, FL
- Met with the production team at the start of the shift to discuss the plan for the day
 Maintained in-house and distribution inventory to report to the sales team
- Transfer finished product to prepare for packaging
- Report to the production manager everything done during the shift

EDUCATION

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development – University of Miami

Miami, FL

September 2020 - March 2021

Bachelor of Business Administration – Florida International University

Miami, FL

August 2016 - May 2020

- Dean's List (4)
- GPA: 3.40/4.00